http://www.zavaletas-guitarras.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy POlicy This Policy applies to information collected on our websites, including without limitation zavaletas-guitarras.com, www.zavaletas-guitars.com, and any associated content, features and functionality contained on or provided through the Website or any of our mobile applications.Please read this Policy carefully and on more than one occasion when you use the Website. By accessing and using this Website on any computer, mobile phone, tablet, console or other device, you signify that you have read and understand the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, you may not access or use the Website.For your convenience, the Website contains links to other websites not under our control. We do not control, are not responsible for, and this Policy does not apply to, the privacy practices or content of those third-party websites. If you decided to initiate a transaction on a website that our Website links to, even if you reached that website through our Website, the information you submit to complete the transaction becomes subject to the privacy practices of the owner of that linked website. You should seek out, carefully read and understand the website privacy policy of each third-party website you visit.INFORMATION Zavaleta’s La Casa De guitarras MAY COLLECT FROM YOUWe may collect personal information from you in several different ways on our Website, including through the use of forms for general inquiries, or through offline contacts such as email, mail or phone calls. This Policy applies to information that you provide to zavaletas-guitarras.com through the Website.We collect this information to provide a more efficient online experience, as well as to provide you with goods and services that you request. Personal information we may collect from you includes your first and last name, language, home or business address, email address, phone number, travel arrangement details, and any other personal information you provide to us. We also collect personal information about you when you purchase products through our website. These financial transactions are processed through third-party service providers with whom we partner but do not control, including https://stripe.com, and http://squarespace.com who will collect personal and financial information from you such as credit card and billing address information, but your financial information is not provided to us. The information collected from you by these third parties is governed by the privacy policies of those third parties and we encourage you to review them. Any personal information we maintain to fulfill your purchase order is subject to this Policy.INFORMATION Zavaleta’s La Casa De guitarras MAY COLLECT AUTOMATICALLYLike most sites, we may automatically collect personal information through the use of “cookies” (small text files in the memory of your browser or device that enable a website to recognize a user’s device), “pixel tags” (small graphic images that typically work in conjunction with cookies to identify users and user behavior) or similar programs, that track information provided by your browser such as the Internet address of your computer, your mobile device ID, the website you came from, the type of computing, mobile or other device used, to track link clicks, page opens, form submissions, and other data that helps us administer our Website, such as the date, time and page(s) you visited on our Website, the duration of your visit and other anonymous information. Some cookies we use enable us to deliver third-party advertising based on your online activity. Most popular Internet browsers will allow you to configure the browser to reject or block cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set, by accessing the “Help” portion of the toolbar. Please refer to your browser for information on how to disable and control cookies and note that if you reject or block cookies it may affect your ability to enjoy the full functionality of our Website.USE AND RETENTION OF INFORMATION BY Zavaleta’s La Casa De guitarrasWe may use the personal information collected from you in several ways. For example, if you indicate on our Website that you would like to receive information about ZAVALETA’S LA CASA DE GUITARRAS  products and services. If you do not wish to provide the requested personal information or if you do not agree to have us use the information for the purposes identified, it is your responsibility to decline use or opt-out of those aspects of our Website for which personal information is sought.The information we collect automatically when you visit our Website is used to analyze general browsing behavior of visitors to our Website, including the popularity of certain pages, and compile statistical reports on site activity, including the daily requests we receive for particular files and which countries those requests came from, so that we can provide a better Website experience. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not names, addresses or other information. This information is used only for internal purposes by zavaletas-guitarras.com technical support staff.We retain personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes of this Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by applicable law or regulation.SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONZavaletas-guitarras.com does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your prior consent.Personal information will not be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information. We may share your personal information with third-party providers that help us provide certain services and functionality such as payment processors. Vendors who would be given access to your personal information solely for the limited purpose of performing the services, or providing the information, you requested and for no other purposes.Our Website may use Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, in order to better understand your use of our websites and how we can improve them. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit a website, what pages you visit when you do so, and what other websites you used prior to coming to such website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit a website, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with your personal information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit a website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to Client websites is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of the Client websites, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected on the Client websites to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. To more fully understand how Google may use the data it collects on the Client websites, please review “How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps,” (located here or any successor URL). LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING INFORMATIONWhere required by the EU General Data Protection with Regulation 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data (“GDPR”), we will only collect and process personal information about you where we have a legal basis. Examples of legal bases include consent (where you have given consent), contract (where processing is necessary for entering into or the performance of a contract with you), and “legitimate interests”. Where we process personal information based on consent, we will ask for your consent. You may withdraw your consent at any time, but that will not affect the lawfulness of the processing of your personal information prior to such withdrawal. Where we rely on contract, we will ask that you agree to the processing of personal information that is necessary for entering into or the performance of your contract with us, and we will inform you whether the provision of your personal data is mandatory and of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information.We may process your personal information for the purposes of our legitimate interests, provided that such processing does not outweigh your rights and freedoms.  Where we rely on legitimate interests, you have the right to object.  We process your personal information based on legitimate interests in order to:·         Market our products and services;·         Protect you, us, or others from data security threats;·         Comply with laws that apply to us; and·         Enable or administer our business, such as for invoicing vendors and customers.DO NOT TRACK SIGNALSCalifornia and Delaware laws require that we indicate whether we honor “Do Not Track” settings in your browser concerning targeted advertising. “Do Not Track” is a standard that is currently under development. As it is not yet finalized, we adhere to the standards set out in this Policy and do not monitor or follow any Do Not Track browser requests.CHILDREN'S POLICYThe Website is intended for a general adult audience and is not intended for children under 16 years of age. zavaletas-guitarras.com does not intentionally collect any personal information from any child under the age of 16 and if we discover we have been provided with any such information, zavaletas-guitarras.com will promptly dispose of the information. zavaletas-guitarras.com encourages parents and guardians to closely monitor children’s online activities.  INTERNATIONAL VISITORSzavaletas-guitarras.com receives visitors from all over the world. If you are accessing this Website from outside the United State of America, please note that your information may be collected, transferred to, stored or processed in the United States and will be subjected to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same privacy protection as the laws of your own country. By continuing to access the Website, you understand and consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities in the United States and those third parties with whom we share it.  For purposes of applicable data protection laws, we will rely on legally-provided mechanisms to lawfully transfer personal data across borders, including consent and performance of a contract.SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTEDWe understand the importance of safeguarding the personal information we collect from you. We therefore take reasonable measures to protect your personal information that is under our control in an effort to prevent its loss, misuse or unauthorized access, alteration or disclosure, including established electronic and administrative safeguards designed to make the information we collect secure. You should take care not to send us personal information in email, which is an inherently insecure form of communication.Although we strive to keep your information secure, no policy or system can perfectly guard against the risk of intentional intrusion or inadvertent disclosure and we do not and cannot guarantee that your information may never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Policy and applicable laws. Any personal information you provide to us is at your own risk. You should understand the limits to privacy and security on the Internet and use common sense in all of your online activities.BUSINESS TRANSITIONSIn the event that zavaletas-guitarras.com and/or its business units or subsidiaries are ever sold, acquired, merged, liquidated, reorganized or otherwise transferred, we reserve the right to transfer our user databases together with any personal information contained therein to a third party acquiring zavaletas-guitarras.com or any of its assets.QUESTIONS OR OPT-OUTIf at any time you have any questions or change your mind and would like to add or remove your name from the zavaletas-guitarras.com mailing list, or update your personal information, or opt out from receiving any further communications from zavaletas-guitarras.com, please either (1) call us at (520) 906-0533, (2) email us at ZAVALETAS@EARTHLINK.NET, (3) click on unsubscribe in the email sent to you, where applicable. EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA (EEA) RESIDENTSUsing the contact details provided above, if you are an EEA resident (specifically, any country in the EU, Lichtenstein, Norway, Iceland), for personal information that we have about you, you can also ask us for a copy of your personal information, ask us to erase or delete all or some of your personal data, ask us to stop using all or some of our personal information or limit our use of it, or ask us for a copy of your personal information provided in machine readable form.If we have collected and processed your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time.  Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.We do not make use of automated decision-making.  As defined under current data protection laws, automated decisions are defined as decisions about individuals that are based solely on the automated (i.e., no human involvement) processing of data and that produce legal effects or that significantly affect the individuals involved.You have the right to complain to a data protection (or supervisory) authority about our collection and use of your personal information.  For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. (Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA and Switzerland are available here.)We respond to all requests that we receive from individuals residing in the EEA and who wish to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.  We may ask you to verify your identity in order to help us respond efficiently to your request.USER SUBMITTED CONTENTYou are solely responsible for your conduct, and for any messages, notes, data, text, information, graphics, photos, audio and video clips, advertisements, listings, links and other content, in any form (“User Submitted Content”) that you submit, upload, publish, post or display on or through zavaletas-guitarras.com channelsYou understand that zavaletas-guitarras.com cannot and does not guarantee the identity of any other User with whom you interact in the course of using the zavaletas-guitarras.com channels. Additionally, we cannot and do not guarantee the authenticity of any data or information that Users may provide about themselves or any other User Submitted Content that is posted or otherwise made available on the zavaletas-guitarras.com channels. You agree that you must evaluate, investigate and bare all risks associated with the use of any User Submitted Content, including reliance on the accuracy, completeness or integrity of such User Submitted Content.You further understand and agree that zavaletas-guitarras.com may preserve User Submitted Content, and may also disclose User Submitted Content, including personally identifiable information (notwithstanding the Privacy Policy), if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce the terms or any other applicable agreement or policy; © respond to claims that any User Submitted Content violates the rights of third parties; or (d) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of zavaletas-guitarras.com, its Users and the public. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, zavaletas-guitarras.com may be required to disclose information pertaining to User Submitted Content to individuals asserting rights under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, and you expressly authorize zavaletas-guitarras.com to comply with any and all lawful notices, subpoenas, court order or warrants without prior notice to you.zavaletas-guitarras SOCIAL MEDIAzavaletas-guitarras.com has numerous accounts across social media platforms that are accessible on or through the zavaletas-guitarras.com websites, as well as directly through the social media platforms themselves. These social media platforms may have their own policies and procedures that govern your use. To the extent that a social media platform does not have its own policies and procedures in place or the policies and procedures do not address topics covered under these Terms, the Terms shall govern your use of all zavaletas-guitarras.com Social Media channels. Without limiting the foregoing, uploading, publishing, posting or displaying the following is expressly prohibited on all zavaletas-guitarras.com Social Media:·         Do not post any content that is disruptive, incendiary, libelous, abusive, vulgar, profane, obscene, hateful, threatening, harassing, defamatory, or which discloses personally identifiable information or private or personal matters concerning any person·         The zavaletas-guitarras.com Facebook page not the place for political or religious discourse·         Do not intentionally make false or misleading statements·         Do not offer to sell or buy any product or service·         Do not post material that infringes any copyright·         Do not post information that you know to be confidential or sensitive or otherwise in the breach of law·         Do not post any content that you don't have the right to post/transmit (and grant us the rights above) under applicable law or under contractual or fiduciary relationship·         Don't impersonate any person, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity·         You represent that all testimonials, endorsements and/or advertisements contained in your posted content are truthful, accurate and represent your opinion and personal experience.zavaletas-guitarras.com observes the right to delete/remove/hide any post, image, video, or content that violates these rules.
